ANDRZEJ LIKOŃSKI | Senior Software Engineer

SUMMARY _____

I am an senior software engineer with more than four years of experience. I also find myself as a fan of Java, maths enthusiast, interested in almost every aspect of tech. I am open for new opportunities to develop my skills not only as software developer but also as a team worker, future architect and mentor. I always pay attention to the details because for me being precise is as important as being effective.

EDUCATION

WROCŁAW UNIVERSITY OF SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY

Engineering degree in Computer Science

Faculty of Electronics

Member Organization of university events such as hackathons (eg. Jelly Pizza Hack). I took a part in various team projects and additional courses.

STUDENTS ORGANIZATION - SISK

EXPERIENCE

INDEPENDENT CONTRACTOR

Self Employed

PRODUCT ENGINEERING SPECIALIST

Accenture

During last three years I gained a lot of knowledge and proved myself in terms of various cloud solutions. I integrated multiple micro-services with REST/SOAP API and message brokers such as Azure Eventhub, Kafka, Solace etc. Besides enhancing my coding skills in Spring and Java I consulted with a clients, designed from scratch and documented a lot of features. I designed and developed a few automation pipelines mostly with Docker, Powershell and Azure Devops tools. In breaks between projects and sometimes as an overtime I had an opportunity to be a team lead in some prove of concept initiatives. Occasionally as a subject matter I worked on offers and cost estimations for business clients. I am a leader of tech meetup that encourage developers to extend their knowledge and a mentor to some interns.

JAVA DEVELOPER

Janmedia Interactive

Designing and implementing features for e-commerce based on specification. Creating software tests and documentation. Taking a part in daily scrum. Refactoring of legacy code.

DEVELOPER

Pronos

Supporting data mining system using Bash and Java. Preparation of IT infrastructure and technical documentation. Design and automation of regression tests.

TRAINEE Reconizer

During internship within an assistance of senior coworkers I implemented few features for Android app and created a documentation of them. I also learned about Firebase (NoSQL database by Google).

10/2014 - 02/2019

Wrocław

05/2016 - 02/2019

Wrocław

08/2022 - Present

Warsaw

04/2019 - 08/2022

Warsaw

06/2018 - 04/2019

Wrocław

03/2018 - 06/2018

Wrocław

07/2017 - 08/2017

Wrocław

SKILLS

CORE SKILLS Java | Spring | Message Brokers | Cloud Architecture | Azure **FRAMEWORKS & TOOLS** Git | Mayen | Docker | SQL | Bash | Powershell

RKS & TOOLS Git | Maven | Docker | SQL | Bash | Powershell LANGUAGES Native: Polish | Fluent: English | Beginner: Italian

Honors & Awards ___

AWARD IN A GOVERNMENT HACKATHON - HACK THE CRISIS

03.2020

Team member

I was a member of a Helpful Neighbour app team on GovTech hackathon organized because of the COVID-19 crisis.

NTERESTS

In my spare time, besides following news about technology and artificial intelligence I love computer games. I have participated in several e-sport events with my friends. I am also a huge fan of old school cars, rock music of the seventies, DIY things and assembling IKEA furniture.

